So you, once you are in thoughtless awareness what happens
所以當你處在無思慮的覺醒中，有什麼會發生呢？
that no thoughts bombard your mind.
那便是沒有任何的想法干擾你的心智
Wherever you may be, you may be in America, you may be in any place.
無論你身處何地，也許你身在美國，也許你身在任何的地方。
You are not bombarded by thoughts.
你都不會被想法所干擾。
So, what does that mean? Into very simple language we can say,
那麼，這意味著什麼呢？我們可以用一個非常簡單的話語去說，
it means that you do not reflect.
這意味著你沒有任何的反應。
You do not have a reflecting mind.
你沒有一個起反應的心智。
Now this is the basic problem of Sahaja Yogis of today,
現在，這個問題對於今天的霎哈嘉瑜伽士來說是一個基礎的問題，
which one should try to conquer.
這個問題是我們應該努力去戰勝的。
That you do not reflect.
那便是你不去作反應。
That's the only way you can achieve your steadiness.
這邊是唯一的方法去實現你的（靈性成長）穩定。
For example I have seen people,
例如，我看見人們
for nothing at all they'll just start laughing,
毫無理由的，他們便開始笑起來，
nothing at all.
毫無理由的。
They see somebody, immediately they react
他們看到某些人，便即刻起了反應
"This was nice but not so good."
“這個挺不錯的，但並不是那麼的好。”
They start giving their opinions, especially in the West, about everything.
他們開始給於他人意見，特別在西方，關於任何的事。
Everybody seems to be very knowledgeable
每一個人似乎看起來都變得非常的博學
and start telling what is best
並且開始述說什麼是最好的
and what is not the best, what is not good.
什麼又是不算最好的，什麼又是不好的。
And once they start saying something like that,
一旦當他們開始像這樣去說話時，
mind becomes reflective.
心智變得具有反射性
If the mind is not reflective, then you are thoughtless awareness.
如果心智沒有反射性，那麼，你便是處在無思慮的覺醒之中。
Watch anything, just you watch.
看任何的事物，只是去看。
Just witness. You should not reflect.
只是去旁觀見證。你不應該去反應。
If you are using your mental power, then this power subsides.
如果你使用你思維的力量，那麼這個靜觀的力量便會下降。
This is a very common defect with people because,
這是一個人們非常普遍的挫敗，因為
I think, you people
我認為，你們
are more intelligent, you think. Maybe
是非常聰慧的，也許你們會想。
I think, you are well educated, might be.
我想你們也許是受到很好的教育的。
I don't know, whatever you think.
我不知道，不管你怎樣認為
But this reflecting mind
但是這個反應的心智
is a very dangerous thing for spirituality.
對於靈性來講是一件非常危險的事情。
You'll never grow. And then with the reflecting mind,
你將不會得到成長。並且伴隨著這個反應的心智
you have different emotions with something you reflect on somebody.
你對某人的反應會有不同的情緒。
Now if it's your son or daughter or something, you get identified.
現在，如果那是你的兒子或女兒或某事，你得到證實。
Identification with some is artificial.
鑑定某些是人工化的。
It's not in reality.
那並不在現實中。
But because this mind reflects, it identifies.
但因為這個心智的反應，他被辨認出。
Now many identifications you have dropped out.
現在，很多鑑定你可以拋棄。
For example your bias about religion,
例如，你對宗教得逞偏見，
about races,
關於 種族，
about maybe nationalities, you have dropped out.
關於 也許是國籍，你可以拋棄。
But still I would say, the reflecting mind still acts
但任然我需要說，這個反應的心智任然在反應
and this is the greatest hurdle for the progress of Sahaja Yogis of today.
這對於今日的霎哈嘉瑜伽士的升進來說，是一個非常巨大的障礙。
I've been thinking "Why is it the reflecting mind
我不得不疑惑“為何如今的起反應的心智
is so active in Sahaja Yogis of today?"
是如此的活躍在霎哈嘉瑜伽士之中。”
If you could stop reflecting,
如果你能夠停止起反應，
immediately you establish yourself
你便立刻建立起了你的
in the ocean of peace.
寧靜的海洋。
You watch something, just watch.
你看一些事，只是看著。
There's no ripple of thought in your mind.
在你的 心智之中沒有任何的漣漪。
Then you become extremely creative.
接著你變得極具創造性。
You become extremely dynamic,
你變得極其有活力，
you become extremely compassionate.
你變得極其有同情心。
You have no fear.
你沒有任何的恐懼。
Some people think, "If you are compassionate
一些人認為"如果你變得具有同情心
you see this man might lynch me". You have no fear.
你看這個人也許會對我處以私刑”。你也沒有任何的恐懼
All virtues that you have to enjoy
所有的虛假的你都可以去享受
you can only enjoy
你可以只是去享受
when you do not reflect.
當你沒有任何反應時
That means that you leave everything to the Divine.
這意味著你讓每一件事來到了神聖之中
You are not in charge.
你沒有任何的責任
You don't see that you have to be reflecting on something.
你不會看到你對某事起反應
This is the greatest power you have got, is not to reflect,
這是你所能夠得到最偉大的力量，便是不去作反應
not to look at somebody with that kind of thing.
不要以這樣一種方式（心智反應）去看某人
I have seen this is still there lingering.
我已經看見這仍在霎哈嘉中被留戀
Perhaps I never told you about it, maybe one of the reasons.
也許我從未告訴過你關於這件事，也許是其中一個原因。
I don't say that it's only your fault but maybe Mine,
我不會說 這僅僅只是你的錯誤，也許是我的。
because I couldn't find what was exactly wrong,
因為我並未能發現什麼是完全的錯誤
that is the reflection that you have about others.
那便是反應這塊，你對與他人的反應
Now I told you, have introspection.
現在我告訴你，需要去內省。
For introspection also it can be reflection,
因為內省也會帶給你反應，
but that at least gives you idea as to where you are.
但起碼它能夠給與你意見，讓你知道你現在去到了哪裡。
But with that psychologically you can become extremely depressed.
但是透過這種心理的方式，你可能變得極其沮喪
You can condemn yourself.
你可以譴責你自己。
Then you may not understand yourself
然後，你可能不理解你自己
as a personality that you are
作為一種你附加的特質
and you'll go on, sort of,
接著你慢慢的，有幾分的，
losing your vibrations, losing your power.
喪失你的生命能量，失去你的力量
Because you are not control of yourself.
因為你不再能夠控制你自己。
So introspection, also, if it brings
所以內省，也，如果 它帶來
about depression and demeaning of your personality,
你的沮喪、貶低特質
best is not to introspect also.
那麼最好也就不要內省了。
Because all these mental activities, I have seen, create problems.
因為所有這些心理的活動，我已經看見，造成了問題。
But in a state where you are thoughtlessly aware,
但是如果你站在的是無思慮的覺醒意識狀態下的話，
introspection comes to you automatically.
內省便會自動的來到於你。
You see it automatically.
你會自動的看見它。
You understand it automatically. You do not think about it,
你理解它的自動化，你對此並不會去想它。
it just comes to you. The whole picture comes to you
它只是來到你之中。這一整個影像來到你之中。
and you are at peace with yourself.
你便與你處在靜默之中。
You are never in turmoil,
你從來不會處在混亂之中
never in trouble.
從來不會處在麻煩之中
Then you don't get angry.
接著你也不會變得生氣。
Then you do not argue,
接著你也不會去去爭論，
then you do not discuss,
接著你也不會去討論，
but you become as if dropped in to the ocean of awareness
但是你成為好像跌入意識的海洋之中。
and you don't have to worry
你也不需要擔憂什麼
as to solve something.
比如去解決某事
When you are reflecting,
當你處在反應之中，
then you find that this power works.
你發現這個力量開始工作。
Now it becomes very contradictory to say that you have to project
現在，它去說變得非常的矛盾，你不得不計劃
and you don't have to reflect.
同時你又不得不不去反應。
Now when we reflect we absorb.
現在，當我們反應 我們便會吸收。
When we reflect on something, we absorb that thing.
當我們在某事上起反應，我們便會吸收這件事
And mostly our attention goes to the defects of others,
並且我們更過的的注意力去到戰勝他人，
"This person is no good, that is not good, this is,
“這個人並不怎麼好，這個也不是太棒，這個是，
her hair is not all right, the sari's not all right."
她的頭髮也並不怎樣，這個莎麗也不怎樣。”
This, that and all nonsense.
這個，那個，所有無意義的廢話。
So what are we doing, we are absorbing all the bad things also.
那麼 我們正在做什麼呢，我們也正在吸收所有這些壞的事。
Now when you start admiration of something.
現在當你開始欣賞某些事物。
Then what happens that you may not get the bad things
那麼什麼會發生呢，就是你不會得到這些會的事物。
but at least you are on a better line.
但至少你正在不錯的路線上。
But still, the admiration in thoughtless awareness
但仍然的，在無思慮的覺醒中去欣賞
is really very deep.
是非常深層的。
I saw this in the eyes of this great scientist.
我通過眼睛去看這個偉大的科學家。
Absolutely he was just one with Me,
完全的 他只是一個人與我一起，
and his eyes were like an ocean of peace.
他的雙眼就像是一片寧靜的海洋。
He was just looking at Me,
他只是看著我，
and for quite some time and then he came to his thoughts
有那麼一會時間，接著他便去到他的思索之中
and he told Me that "This is what we can do with Your photograph."
他告訴我：“這便是在你的相片上我們所能過做到的了。”
So the depth in you will only come when you do not reflect.
所以你內在的深度只能透過你行無反應到來。
But it's very common with human beings, specially in the West,
但這對於人類來說是很普遍的，特別對於西方來講，
"this carpet is no good, that is no good,
“這個地毯不怎麼好，那個也不好，
this smell is coming, that is there,"
這個味道也來了，這裡散發出來的。”
always trying to judge others,
總是在努力判斷他人，
judge other things.
判斷其他的事情。
This is important? What is so important?
這個很重要嗎？那什麼又是更重要的？
If you are sitting in the garden of heavens
如果你坐在天空的花園
what does it matter where you are sitting, what you are doing?
你坐在哪裡，這又有什麼關係呢 ？你又正在做什麼呢？
This sets in, this reflection, sets in waves of thoughts in our mind.
這個反應設定在這裡的，設置在我們心智想法的波浪之中。
I have already, once, described it by drawing.
我早已經，曾經，通過繪畫描述過它。
How the energy that falls on the right side
這一能量是如何從右脈降落
goes to the left side
去到左脈
and the falls on the left goes to the right.
又如何從左邊降落去到右邊
Crosses over because of two types of cells we have.
交叉跨越，因為我們擁有兩個不同類型的細胞。
Then out of this energy that goes to the right,
接著從這個能量去到右邊
the energy that goes to the left
這個能量去到左邊
it is sucked in partly into the sympathetic.
它會被部分地吸收到交感神經
Now whatever is left out is the one that reflects.
現在無論什麼從左邊出來都是一個反應
That is the way it goes on reflecting.
這便是一個方法讓它繼續做反應。
Now if you can suck in all that energy and put it on our sympathetic,
現在 如果你可以吸收所有這些能量 並將它放置到我們的交感神經上，
then all our energies will be thousand fold much more.
那麼 我們所有的能量都將會被上千次以上的摺疊。